<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE MudletPackage>
<MudletPackage version="1.001">
	<ScriptPackage>
		<Script isActive="yes" isFolder="no">
			<name>DefaultYATCOConversion</name>
			<packageName></packageName>
			<script>-- These are the same as the default YATCO options on a 1080p monitor. 
demonnic = demonnic or {}
demonnic.chat = demonnic.chat or EMCO:new({
  -- these are the x and y coordinates for the top-left of the tabbed container
  x = 1486,
  y = 0,
  -- height and width of the overall tabbed box
  width = 419,
  height = 705,
  -- display timestamps and format it
  timestamp = true,
  timestampFormat = "HH:mm:ss",
  -- we do not use a custom color for the timestamp by default
  customTimestampColor = false,
  -- but we do define the colors anyways, as an example/
  timestampFGColor = "red",
  timestampBGColor = "blue",
  -- what names to give to the console. This is what shows up in the tabs
  consoles = {
    "All",
    "City",
    "Guild",
    "Clans",
    "Local"
  },
  -- do you want to have a tab which displays everything? defaults to true
  allTab = true,
  -- the tab everything gets sent to is called 'All'. Make sure that whatever you put here is also in consoles above.
  allTabName = "All",
  -- do we want one of the tabs to display the Mudlet mapper? Set to false if not (default) but if so
  -- change to the name of the tab you want to show the map. "Map" or "Local" or whatever you like. Make
  -- sure it appears in the consoles list above
  mapTab = false,
  -- should we blink tabs to draw your attention to new information?
  blink = true,
  -- if you're looking at the all tab, should we blink anyway? 
  blinkFromAll = false,
  -- font size for all the miniconsoles
  fontSize = 9,
  -- should we make sure the background in the miniconsole never changes from the consoleColor/css background?
  preserveBackground = false,
  -- also include a deleteLine() when doing append()s?
  gag = false,
  -- what color should we make the active tab? Defaults to green. Can use any name from showColors
  activeTabBGColor = "&lt;0,180,0&gt;",
  -- what color should the inactive tabs be? Defaults to a lightish grey
  inactiveTabBGColor = "&lt;60,60,60&gt;",
  -- what color to make the console background? This is the main section where the text is displayed
  consoleColor = "&lt;0,0,0&gt;",
  -- what color should the text in the active tab be? 
  activeTabFGColor = "purple",
  -- and the inactive tab text color
  inactiveTabFGColor = "white"
})
--- End script</script>
			<eventHandlerList />
		</Script>
	</ScriptPackage>
</MudletPackage>
